https://micamedical.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We at MICA are committed to maintain the privacy and security of our customers’ personal information on this site. Through this privacy statement, MICA Information Systems, Inc., wants to assure you of our commitment to privacy and security.
MICA operates by the following principles:
We will not ask for information that personally identifies you (“Private, Sensitive Information”) while you are simply browsing our Public Site, http://www.micamedical.com. If this should change, we will explain what the information for which we are asking is to be used.
If you request to download a software demo from our Public Site, we might ask for personal information. This information will only be used for tracking purposes or to contact you personally. This information will never be shared outside of MICA.
If you are visiting a MICA Secure Site, to which access is limited to our Business Alliance Partners, we may collect the personal information that you specifically and knowingly provide. The use of such information will be governed by the specific written contract between you and MICA through which you were granted access to such MICA Secure Site.
In addition, on a MICA Secure Site such as our support site, we may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of the Secure Site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our information handling practices, or any other aspects of your privacy, please send an e-mail to: support@micamedical.com.  Our mailing address is: 1580 Westbrook Plaza Drive, Winston Salem, NC  27103
MICA may periodically update this policy to describe how new Web features may affect our use of your information and to let you know of new controls and features that we may provide you.
MICA will NOT apply changes to this policy retroactively to information MICA has previously collected.
“MICA/IMS was one of the best decisions we have ever made in selecting a Practice Management Software module. The fact that it integrates so well with Availity, e-prescriptions, EMR, Auto-Confirm and so on makes it an A-1 product in my book and I have been working with this type of software for many, many years.”
Roy S.
Practice Manager
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:03:16-04:00
Roy S.
Practice Manager
“MICA/IMS was one of the best decisions we have ever made in selecting a Practice Management Software module. The fact that it integrates so well with Availity, e-prescriptions, EMR, Auto-Confirm and so on makes it an A-1 product in my book and I have been working with this type of software for many, many years.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3469/
“We are a 6-provider Dermatology practice and have used MICA Information Systems since we opened in 2009. From our original Practice Management software, to our EMR system, to billing and IT support, the owners and staff of MICA have always been there for us.
When you call your billing, software or IT support company, do they know your name? Ours doe. It is very refreshing to hear "Hi Robert" when I call. You are not a client number with MICA.”
Robert B.
Practice Manager
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:04:28-04:00
Robert B.
Practice Manager
“We are a 6-provider Dermatology practice and have used MICA Information Systems since we opened in 2009. From our original Practice Management software, to our EMR system, to billing and IT support, the owners and staff of MICA have always been there for us. When you call your billing, software or IT support company, do they know your name? Ours doe. It is very refreshing to hear "Hi Robert" when I call. You are not a client number with MICA.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3472/
“Whenever we have an issue (which isn't often), staff members from Marlo to Scott or Jim or others take the time to personally resolve it promptly...not just "pass the buck" like customer service at many other larger companies.”
Stephen F.
Counselor
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:04:57-04:00
Stephen F.
Counselor
“Whenever we have an issue (which isn't often), staff members from Marlo to Scott or Jim or others take the time to personally resolve it promptly...not just "pass the buck" like customer service at many other larger companies.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3473/
“The current IMS build is very user adaptable. Working with my staff, MICA preloaded our common CPT's, ICD-10's, and favorite medications. They created forms, letters, etc. that greatly facilitated our transition to electronic workflow. They have been very responsive to software issues and requested fixes.”
Erik K., MD
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:05:54-04:00
Erik K., MD
“The current IMS build is very user adaptable. Working with my staff, MICA preloaded our common CPT's, ICD-10's, and favorite medications. They created forms, letters, etc. that greatly facilitated our transition to electronic workflow. They have been very responsive to software issues and requested fixes.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3475/
“I have used Mica Information Systems for the past 20+ years for our 5-office Allergy practice.
We recently incorporated IMS into our practice through Mica's strong support team and we absolutely love it.
From software to hardware it is allowing our Allergy practice to be more efficient.
They are always there to answer our questions and provide support.”
Sally B.
Practice Manager
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:06:24-04:00
Sally B.
Practice Manager
“I have used Mica Information Systems for the past 20+ years for our 5-office Allergy practice. We recently incorporated IMS into our practice through Mica's strong support team and we absolutely love it. From software to hardware it is allowing our Allergy practice to be more efficient. They are always there to answer our questions and provide support.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3476/
“The functionality of the scheduling module is so much better than our previous system.
We have noticed that our documentation is better and more extensive, we are able to do better follow up on our patients that require periodic testing, scanning and lab work. The accounts receivable is much easier to follow up on and work.”
Karen S.
Practice Manager
MICA Information Systems
2020-08-04T13:06:42-04:00
Karen S.
Practice Manager
“The functionality of the scheduling module is so much better than our previous system. We have noticed that our documentation is better and more extensive, we are able to do better follow up on our patients that require periodic testing, scanning and lab work. The accounts receivable is much easier to follow up on and work.”
https://micamedical.com/testimonials/3479/
0
0
MICA Information Systems
Follow Us on Our Social Networks
Information
Home
Billing & PM
Monday - Friday: 8:00 a.m. - 5:30 p.m.24/7 Technical Support also available
Sitemap
Copyright © 2020 MICA Information Systems, Inc.
All rights reserved.
Web Design and Domain names by
